CURRICULUMVITAE ADAM TAHA CURRICULUMVITAE

CREATIVE MIND LOOKING FOR AN APPRENTICESHIP



Transforming ideas into captivating realities.

I am a young and ambitious man who likes to create things and see them come to life. My curiosity drives me to constantly try new things and expand my cultural horizons. I enjoy meeting new people and learning from them, with the hope of sharing my knowledge with others someday.

Since I don't set limits to my learning, I have gained many skills in multimedia, allowing me to combine my expertise in developing and design to my imagination and creativity, making me a driving force in a team.

CONTACT

Email Adress: adamtaha2001@gmail.com

Phone Number: +33 6 12 94 06 13

LinkedIn: adam-taha

Portfolio: Click Here!

HOBBIES

Acting and Directing Cinema
Football and Gym Travel

LANGUAGES

French: Native Arabic: B1
English: C1 Spanish: A2

Japanese: B1 Russian: Notions

SOFT SKILLS

Creativity Leadership
Flexibility Sociable
Great Speaker Team Work

HARD SKILLS

COMPUTER SCIENCE

HTML 5 / CSS 3 JAVASCRIPT
Flutter / Dart PHP - MySQL
Unity - C# WordPress CMS

DESIGN AND VIDEO

ADOBE Photoshop ADOBE Premiere Pro
ADOBE Illustrator ADOBE After Effects

ADOBE In Design Da Vinci Resolve

UX / UI Design CapCut

OTHER Figma

PowerPoint & Excel Agile Methodology

WORK EXPERIENCE -

Freelance Worker - since 2024

• Working on missions for clients (Web Design, Graphic Design, Editing...)

Web Manager - 2023 - 2024

COMMOKA - OKAYAMA, JAPAN

- · Management of the website and its content.
- Updating the website according to the chief's demands.
- Creation of content: pages, articles, videos, and social media posts.

Game Designer - January to June 2023

COMMOKA - OKAYAMA, JAPAN

- \bullet Creation of brand new video game based on Japanese mythology
- Level designing and coding the many scripts (with UNITY)
- Making of original visual assets for the game (with ILLUSTRATOR)

Web Designer - June to September 2023

COMMOKA - OKAYAMA, JAPAN (Internship)

- Making a brand new website for a communication company
- Creation of wireframe, user journeys, user testing
- \bullet Creation of a visual identity and graphic chart for the company

Community Manager - April 2019 to August 2022

BIG CHEF RESTAURANT - VILLETANEUSE, FRANCE

- Creation of content on social media (Twitter, Instagram, Snapchat)
- Interaction with the clients, limited offers, events

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

University Sorbonne Paris Nord - Bobigny - since 2021

BUT MMI- Bachelor in Multimedia and Internet Technologies

- Web Development and Interactive Design, Front & Back
- Computer Graphics and Audiovisual
- Communication and Marketing, UX / UI Design

Hotel School Albert de Mun - Paris VII - 2020/2021

BTS- Hotel and Catering

- Traditional French Cuisine
- Table and Room Service

Fordham University - New York - Summer 2019

- Studies on English language in international classes
- Certification of language level C1 (CECRL)

Scientific Baccalaureate - Courbevoie - 2019

CURRICULUMVITAE ADAM TAHA CURRICULUMVITAE

ESPRIT CREATIF A LA RECHERCHE D'UNE ALTERNANCE



Transformer les idées en réalités captivantes.

Je suis un jeune homme ambitieux qui aime créer des choses et les voir prendre vie. Ma curiosité me pousse à essayer de nouvelles choses et à élargir mes horizons. J'aime rencontrer de nouvelles personnes et apprendre d'elles, dans l'espoir de partager un jour mes connaissances avec les autres.

Comme je ne fixe pas de limites à mon apprentissage, j'ai acquis de nombreuses compétences en multimédia, ce qui me permet de combiner mon expertise en développement et en design avec mon imagination et ma créativité, faisant de moi un élément moteur dans une équipe.

CONTACT

Adresse mail: adamtaha2001@gmail.com

Numéro Tel: +33 6 12 94 06 13

LinkedIn: adam-taha

Portfolio: Cliquez ici!

PASSIONS

Comédien et Réalisateur Cinéma
Football et Gym Voyager

LANGUES

Français: Natif Arabe: B1

Anglais: C1 Espagnol: A2

Japonais: B1 Russe: Notions

SOFT SKILLS

Créatif Leadership

Esprit d'Équipe Orateur
Flexible Sociable

HARD SKILLS

DEVELOPPEMENT WEB

HTML 5 / CSS 3 JAVASCRIPT
Flutter / Dart PHP - MySQL
Unity - C# WordPress CMS

CREATION NUMERIQUE

ADOBE Photoshop ADOBE Premiere Pro
ADOBE Illustrator ADOBE After Effects

ADOBE In Design Da Vinci Resolve

UX / UI Design CapCut

AUTRES Fiama

PowerPoint & Excel Agile Methodology

— EXPERIENCE PROFESSIONNELLE —

Créateur Freelance - depuis 2024

• Missions pour des clients japonais (design graphique, montage vidéo...)

Responsable Web - 2023 - 2024

COMMOKA - OKAYAMA, JAPAN

- · Gestion du site web et de son contenu
- Mise à jour du site web selon les souhaits du chef d'entreprise.
- Création de contenu : articles, vidéos et publications sur les réseaux sociaux.

Game Designer - Janvier à Juin 2023

COMMOKA - OKAYAMA, JAPAN

- Création d'un tout nouveau jeu vidéo basé sur la mythologie japonaise
- Level Design et codage de nombreux scripts (avec UNITY)
- Création d'éléments visuels originaux pour le jeu (avec ILLUSTRATOR)

Web Designer - Juin à Septembre 2023

COMMOKA - OKAYAMA, JAPAN (Internship)

- \bullet Création d'un nouveau site internet pour une entreprise de communication
- $\bullet \ \mathsf{R\'ealisation} \ \mathsf{de} \ \mathsf{maquettes} \text{, \'elaboration} \ \mathsf{d'un} \ \mathsf{parcours} \ \mathsf{utilisateurs} \text{, user-test}.$
- · Création d'une nouvelle identité visuelle et d'une charte graphique.

Community Manager - Avril 2019 à Août 2022

BIG CHEF RESTAURANT - VILLETANEUSE, FRANCE

- Création de contenu sur les réseaux sociaux (Twitter, Instagram, Snapchat)
- Interaction avec les clients, offres limitées, événements, concours

PARCOURS SCOLAIRE

University Sorbonne Paris Nord - Bobigny - depuis 2021

BUT MMI- Bachelor en Métiers du Multimedia et d'Internet

- \bullet Développement Web et Dispositifs Interactifs, Front & Back
- · Graphisme, Audiovisuel
- Communication et Marketing, Design UI / UX

École Hôtelière Albert de Mun - Paris VII - 2020/2021

BTS- Hôtellerie - Restauration

- Cuisine traditionnelle française
- \bullet Service à Table et Service de Chambre

Fordham University - New York - Été 2019

- Cours d'anglais dans des classes internationales
- Certification du niveau C1 en anglais (CECRL)

Baccalauréat Scientifique - Courbevoie - 2019